My Lord, the Snow Dragon Whisker
has been found.
Where is it?
In the Crown Prince's hands.
After the great fire in Qingzhou,
the Nanyue royal family,
seeking the Crown Prince's favor,
secretly sent him a ten-year-nurtured
Snow Dragon Whisker seed
via the black market.
Only by bringing down the Crown Prince
can we get the Snow Dragon Whisker.
Got it.
No matter what,
we need to wake up my father first.
As for Mei Lin…
It's an Undying Flower.
When I went out of the palace today,
I saw some Undying Flowers.
His Majesty will be fine.
Is there a problem
with the Emperor's antidote?
It's easy to prepare the antidote,
but it's very hard to take it
into the Yanming Palace.
If the Crown Prince realizes
we've uncovered
that my father was poisoned,
he will become desperate
and act recklessly.
At that time,
my father will be in real danger.
What's your plan?
To detoxify my father,
we can only secretly seek
Liu Zhong's assistance.
But it's very difficult to see Liu Zhong.
Maybe one person can help us.
Concubine Yan visits the lotus pond
at the Chen and You hours daily
to release an Eternal Life Ship
in prayer for the Emperor.
WISH THE EMPEROR GOOD HEALTH
We can send her a message
through the Eternal Life Ship.
WITHIN THREE FEET
ALL ILLNESSES VANISH
The gods have manifested.
Look, Your Highness.
It's the Eternal Life Ship.
Within three feet, all illnesses vanish.
This is Mei Lin's writing.
What does she mean?
Mei Lin has found a deity
who can save His Majesty.
Let's go to Yanming Palace.
Her Highness will surely recognize
my writing
and send the Eternal Life Ship
to Yanming Palace.
However, due
to your relationship with her,
she is likely under constant surveillance
by the Crown Prince.
YANMING PALACE
Your Highness.
What are you holding?
This is the Eternal Life Ship
I used for my prayers.
If placed within three feet
of His Majesty's bedside,
he will surely recover
from all his ailments.
Look.
This is specially made secret ink.
Without my prompt,
no one else can see the hidden message.
Concubine Yan will provide them
with an ordinary Eternal Life Ship
for blessings.
It won't raise suspicion.
His Majesty did not dote on you in vain.
However, your intentions
might not be able to get through.
YANMING PALACE
- Eunuch Liu.
- Your Highness.
I understand your good intentions.
Once His Majesty wakes,
he will understand them as well.
Please go back to Fanghua Palace.
Eunuch Liu,
look, this is a deity of Great Yan.
It's sure to work.
WITHIN THREE FEET
ALL ILLNESSES VANISH
Will Eunuch Liu accept
the Eternal Life Ship for blessings?
As long as he sees
the portrait of Shennong,
he'll accept it.
Rebel! Trying to drive me to my grave?
Father,
I know I was wrong.
Father, if you harm yourself in anger,
I would be beyond redemption.
This gesture shows you admit your mistake.
Eunuch Liu taught me that.
Reflecting on my childhood mischief,
I was fortunate
to have Eunuch Liu's secret help,
sparing me much suffering.
I will hint to Eunuch Liu
how to read the secret message
using the portrait of Shennong.
Your Highness, was this portrait
of Shennong painted by you?
Eunuch Liu,
it's the manifestation of gods.
Please give it a try. It will work.
Your Highness.
Bring me some ginger slices and vinegar.
Yes.
My father did not suffer a stroke.
He was poisoned by the Crown Prince.
The conflict between the incense
and the tonics caused his coma.
Your Majesty.
Mei Lin, Eunuch Liu
has received the message.
We have succeeded.
Really?
My father should wake up very soon.
You didn't sleep well these days.
Take a nap.
But I'm too happy to fall asleep.
Would you like to try the method
you used to help me fall asleep
in the Court of State Ceremonial?
Do you want to knock me out?
I can't bear to do so.
My Lord,
the medicine you ordered is ready.
Are you ill?
This is a soothing soup
I prepared for you.
It helps with sleep
and is good for your health.
This medicine is so bitter.
We agreed to share
both good and hard times together.
It truly is very bitter.
Take a nap.
YANMING PALACE
If my father is unable to open his mouth
or take any liquids,
place the antidote in the incense burner
and let it fume
for one incense stick each day.
The toxins may clear after three days.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty. Your Majesty.
Stop!
What are you doing?
What do you want to do?
- Your Highness.
- Eunuch Liu.
I just want to release
an Eternal Life Ship for blessings
for His Majesty.
Do you have to stop me?
So, you are seeking help from the gods,
not my third brother.
- Arrest him.
- Yes.
- What are you doing?
- Go. Go.
Your Highness,
I just want to pray for blessings.
I want to pray for blessings
for His Majesty.
Without Eunuch Liu,
Jinghe will seek Luomei's help.
Keep a close watch,
especially on Mei Lin.
Yes.
PRINCE JING'S MANSION
My Lord, Eunuch Liu has been
captured by the Crown Prince.
The only person who can rescue Eunuch Liu
without alerting the Crown Prince's spies
is General Yin.
However, we received no reply
to our previous messages to her.
The day after tomorrow
will be my final inspection of the camp.
By then,
I will present to the court
a well-disciplined Pingnan Army
with clear defense protocols.
Go to the West Suburban Guard Post.
Today is General Yin's last inspection
of the camp.
There aren't many spies in the army.
This is our last chance.
Greetings, General.
- Greetings, General.
Today is my last inspection of the camp.
From now on,
even though I will no longer
be in the army,
the Pingnan Army must keep their oaths
and protect the people of Great Yan.
I, Yin Luomei,
will always be a comrade
of the Pingnan Army.
Remove the armor. Take down the flag.
YIN
YAN
Farewell, General!
Who are you? Come out.
General Yin, it's me.
I've come to deliver a message
from Prince Jing.
How dare you trespass
into the military camp?
Aren't you afraid I would kill you?
I know you
and General Weibei
are both humane commanders
who would not kill innocents
indiscriminately.
The General's Mansion won't participate
in the struggle for succession.
I can't give Prince Jing what he wants.
TO GENERAL YIN
Please read the letter, General.
How dare you
enter the tent
without announcing yourself!
Please pardon me, Your Highness.
The Crown Prince has important matters
to discuss with you.
Please return to the palace
as soon as possible.
PERSONALLY ADDRESSED TO GENERAL YIN
You go back first.
After addressing military affairs,
I will return to the palace.
Yes.
Tell Prince Jing
that I am now the Crown Princess.
No matter what happens,
I will stand with the Eastern Palace.
If he tries to sow discord again,
don't blame me for showing no mercy
despite our past.
Jiangtu,
escort her back to Prince Jing's Mansion.
Yes.
Set up a perimeter one li away.
No one is allowed to approach.
Yes.
I didn't expect you still remember
how to beat the Great Yan charge drum.
Only General Weibei
would add an extra beat
to the three rounds.
You went to such great lengths
for the sake of the struggle
for succession?
The struggle for succession
began ten years ago.
The Qingzhou matter was settled long ago.
Even now, do you still want
to blame the Crown Prince?
Do you remember
the strategist Li Qing
in the eldest prince's mansion?
I heard he was a spy from Xiyan.
Wasn't he executed?
That was merely Xuanlie's own explanation.
Li Qing was planted
in the Ministry of Defense.
The Qingzhou massacre
was orchestrated by him and Zhang Yin.
Anticipating that
Xuanlie would eliminate witnesses,
he devised a plan
to hide in the West Mountain Mine.
So, during the Lushan Hunt,
you deliberately disappeared to find him?
That's right.
Now, Li Qing is in my mansion.
This is his confession.
The evidence and witnesses are all here.
If you still have doubts,
you are welcome to verify them.
The Crown Prince feared I would
return and overturn the case,
so he administered
a slow-acting poison to our father.
Eunuch Liu has been imprisoned
by the Crown Prince
for secretly giving our father
an antidote.
Now, the only one who can save Eunuch Liu
is you.
The Yin family has always been loyal.
At this critical moment for Great Yan,
I hope you can act decisively
and turn the situation around.
I failed to prevent Prince Jing's
people from acting.
But the Crown Princess burnt the letter
and said
in any situation,
she would stand by Your Highness.
Got it.
How is the interrogation
of Liu Zhong going?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
An expert executioner
can break even the strongest will
within two days.
Liu Zhong has always favored Prince Jing.
Planning to assassinate the Crown Prince
while exploiting the Emperor's illness
to secure the throne for Prince Jing.
If he signs this confession,
Prince Jing will surely face death.
Eunuch Liu,
for my third brother,
you are so cruel to yourself.
I would rather die than let you prevail.
When you will die
is up to me.
General Yin. Please stop, General Yin.
General Yin,
the Crown Prince committed regicide
and treason by poisoning the Emperor.
He killed 100,000 Qingzhou…
General Yin, you've misjudged him.
Kill me and save His Majesty.
Scoundrel, how dare you slander me!
When Luomei dons her armor,
she leads the Pingnan Army
of 30,000 as a general.
When she removes her armor,
she leads me alone as the Crown Princess.
Your Highness,
as the heir apparent of Great Yan,
you are known
for your benevolence and kindness,
loving your people
as a father loves his children.
No matter what happens,
I will stand by you.
Didn't you promise to stand with me
in defending Great Yan?
The Yin family has always been loyal.
At this critical moment for Great Yan,
I hope you can act decisively
and turn the situation around.
Luomei.
You schemed against my aunt
and the entire Yin family.
As a daughter of the Yin family,
do I have a choice?
Yes.
It was me.
I schemed against Jinghe,
and I schemed for the throne.
I plotted against everything
within my sight.
But I never schemed against you.
So, what they said is all true.
Why?
Because in your eyes,
there is forever only Murong Jinghe.
If it weren't for my decisive actions
in Qingzhou
that caused Jinghe to lose
the people's support,
how could my father make me
the Crown Prince?
And how could I stand
before you like this,
so that you could see me?
Luomei, you have promised me a lifetime.
I won't allow you to take it back.
I spared his life
regarding the Qingzhou incident,
but he refuses to let it go,
insisting on overturning the verdict,
disrupting you and me,
and ruining everything.
As long as he is around,
I will always be the loser.
Slap me again.
Even to this day,
you show no remorse whatsoever.
Slap me until you are no longer angry.
This slap
is for all the wronged souls in Qingzhou.
is for His Majesty who placed
high hopes in you.
This slap
is for myself.
I falsely claim to be loyal
to the Emperor and the country.
I actually fell in love with you.
Just pretend that nothing happened.
It was me who plotted treason.
Everything is unrelated to you.
Luomei, trust me.
I will fulfill what I promised you.
XIEYING PAVILION
The Red Fruit has sprouted.
It's a good sign.
I wish General Yin can bring us good news.
How could it be so hot?
I just caught a cold.
It's nothing.
The leeches are alive.
But if you want to persist on,
it will harm your health.
I can endure it.
The medicine is ready.
My lord, after taking the medicine,
you will feel better.
Physician,
he doesn't seem to have caught a cold.
What's the matter with him?
- He…
- You may leave now.
I'll take my leave.
You are hiding something from me.
- Nothing.
- You still say there is nothing.
I smelled your medicine just now.
There is Xuanhu in it.
It's for killing pain.
Are you wounded?
I really can't hide anything from you.
This is an old ailment from Qingzhou.
Damp weather makes the pain unbearable.
After taking the medicine,
I will recover very soon.
You hid it from me again.
Why are you always like this?
- I'm just afraid…
- Afraid I would worry?
Jinghe,
you have to promise me.
No matter what happens in the future,
don't hide anything from me.
Assassinate Murong Jinghe.
You acted on your own
and betrayed the Shadow Works.
You should meet your end.
- Mei Lin, actually, I…
- My lord.
My lord, something happened.
The Eastern Palace sent this to us.
Eunuch Liu died. General Yin killed him.
What should we do now?
The Emperor's antidote
must not be interrupted
or all previous efforts will be in vain.
I can ask Concubine Yan for help.
Right.
Concubine Yan is a consort of Great Yan
and also the princess of Xiyan.
Now, only she can enter
the Yanming Palace.
I only need to sneak
into the Fanghua Palace
and give her the antidote.
Remember, no matter what happens,
don't leave Fanghua Palace.
Okay.
PRINCE JING'S MANSION
Be careful.
Keep my hairpin well.
If it is damaged,
you'll have to spend your life
making it up to me.
Wait for me to come back.
I will protect it well.
When you come back,
I will tell you everything.
I only wish that at that time,
you would still promise me a lifetime.
My lord.
My lord. My lord.
FANGHUA PALACE
Chagu.
- Your Highness.
- Chagu,
have you found out where Eunuch Liu is?
Your Highness, rumors are spreading
that Eunuch Liu fell critically ill
and passed away last night.
How could this be?
Your Highness, if His Majesty passes away,
you'll have nobody
to rely on in the palace.
Let's listen to the Prince Heir
and go back to Xiyan.
No, I can't go.
If I leave, what about His Majesty?
The Prince Heir said
His Majesty has arranged
everything for you.
If you don't leave,
you will be betraying
His Majesty's goodwill.
His Majesty has arranged
everything for me.
How could I leave
when he is in such peril?
But if you don't leave, what can you do?
I…
Your Highness.
Mei Lin. Mei Lin.
Mei Lin.
- You are drenched.
- Your Highness.
Chagu, fetch some dry clothes.
Your Highness, we've found a way
to save His Majesty.
Now, only you can save him.
Me?
- How is it?
- The leeches are dead.
Well, what about Prince Jing?
The excruciating pain,
which even Xuanhu cannot suppress,
has caused Prince Jing to pass out.
This detoxification method
may not succeed.
Moreover, such pain is unbearable
for an ordinary person.
It was me who caused her
to be poisoned with Momai.
No matter how painful, I should endure it.
When the Emperor wakes,
we can bring down the Crown Prince.
Then we can get the Snow Dragon Whisker.
Why must you put yourself in danger?
I dare not bet on the only choice.
One more method of detoxification,
for her, is one more chance to survive.
You must first ingest the poison.
Then I can use your body
to test the leech detoxification method.
You will have to endure the pain
of the leeches' bites.
If you can't hold on,
you must take the antidote promptly,
or it will endanger your own life.
But Prince Jing has taken the antidote.
He should wake up very soon.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
how is His Majesty?
Concubine Yan, you don't understand
the rules of attending to the sick.
I will oversee things here
at the Yanming Palace.
You may go back.
Your Highness,
His Majesty can't wake up, can he?
Don't talk nonsense.
But everyone in the palace said so.
I beg you, Your Highness.
Please let me in to see His Majesty.
I know I'm useless.
I can't cure His Majesty,
but I just want to stay with him.
Let me go in. I beg you.
Your Highness. Your Highness.
I beg you, Your Highness.
Please let me in to see His Majesty.
Your Highness.
I beg you, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
His Majesty treated me so well.
I just want to stay with him.
Let me go in, okay?
I beg you, Your Highness.
Get up.
You agreed, right?
Your Highness, you…
Anyone wishing to enter
must be searched first.
Yanming Palace is heavily guarded.
Only by becoming the antidote myself
can I avoid detection during a search.
Go in now.
Thank you, Your Highness.
- Catch her.
- Yes.
Follow me.